let questions29 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "bomb",
      answer: "B. Sprengkörper",
      options: [
        "A. Geschenk",
        "B. Sprengkörper",
        "C. Werkzeug",
        "D. Spielzeug"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "certificate",
      answer: "C. Urkunde",
      options: [
        "A. Tagebuch",
        "B. Rechnung",
        "C. Urkunde",
        "D. Zeitschrift"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "circumstance",
      answer: "D. Umstand",
      options: [
        "A. Hoffnung",
        "B. Wunsch",
        "C. Traum",
        "D. Umstand"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "coffin",
      answer: "A. Sarg",
      options: [
        "A. Sarg",
        "B. Schublade",
        "C. Koffer",
        "D. Schrank"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "to cope",
      answer: "C. bewältigen",
      options: [
        "A. versagen",
        "B. aufgeben",
        "C. bewältigen",
        "D. vermeiden"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "criticism",
      answer: "B. Kritik",
      options: [
        "A. Lob",
        "B. Kritik",
        "C. Ermutigung",
        "D. Vorschlag"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "to devastate",
      answer: "D. zerstören",
      options: [
        "A. bauen",
        "B. reparieren",
        "C. erschaffen",
        "D. zerstören"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to frown",
      answer: "A. stirnrunzeln",
      options: [
        "A. stirnrunzeln",
        "B. lächeln",
        "C. jubeln",
        "D. winken"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "to gaze",
      answer: "C. starren",
      options: [
        "A. übersehen",
        "B. beobachten",
        "C. starren",
        "D. ignorieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to glance",
      answer: "B. flüchtig blicken",
      options: [
        "A. studieren",
        "B. flüchtig blicken",
        "C. untersuchen",
        "D. fokussieren"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "grief",
      answer: "D. Trauer",
      options: [
        "A. Freude",
        "B. Aufregung",
        "C. Hoffnung",
        "D. Trauer"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "groom",
      answer: "A. Bräutigam",
      options: [
        "A. Bräutigam",
        "B. Diener",
        "C. Bruder",
        "D. Onkel"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "license",
      answer: "C. Erlaubnis",
      options: [
        "A. Geheimnis",
        "B. Vertrag",
        "C. Erlaubnis",
        "D. Gesetz"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "microscope",
      answer: "B. Mikroskop",
      options: [
        "A. Teleskop",
        "B. Mikroskop",
        "C. Kamera",
        "D. Fernglas"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "nuclear",
      answer: "D. atomar",
      options: [
        "A. natürlich",
        "B. organisch",
        "C. chemisch",
        "D. atomar"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "to portray",
      answer: "A. darstellen",
      options: [
        "A. darstellen",
        "B. verbergen",
        "C. ignorieren",
        "D. erfinden"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "to rotate",
      answer: "C. drehen",
      options: [
        "A. stoppen",
        "B. fixieren",
        "C. drehen",
        "D. stillstehen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "souvenir",
      answer: "B. Andenken",
      options: [
        "A. Werkzeug",
        "B. Andenken",
        "C. Dokument",
        "D. Geld"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "submarine",
      answer: "D. Unterseeboot",
      options: [
        "A. Hubschrauber",
        "B. Flugzeug",
        "C. Schiff",
        "D. Unterseeboot"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "to trace",
      answer: "A. nachzeichnen",
      options: [
        "A. nachzeichnen",
        "B. verwischen",
        "C. verbergen",
        "D. zerstören"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions29;